Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Business Papers (Box 698-751, OV 868-OV 869)
  - The John Gary Show
    - Contracts: Guest Contracts
      - Ames, Ed (Box-folder 748/2)
      - Amsterdam, Morey (Box-folder 748/3)
      - Armstrong, Judy (Box-folder 748/4)
      - Arnold, Eddy (Box-folder 748/5)
      - Banner, John (Box-folder 748/6)
      - Barrett, Susan (Box-folder 748/7)
      - Bryant, Anita (Box-folder 748/8)
      - Byner, John (Box-folder 748/9)
      - Cambridge, Godfrey (Box-folder 748/10)
      - Carr, Vikki (Box-folder 748/11)
      - Chad & Jeremy (Box-folder 748/12)
      - Clooney, Rosemary (Box-folder 748/13)
      - Conway, Tim (Box-folder 748/14)
      - Crane, Bob (Box-folder 748/15)
      - Crosby, Norm (Box-folder 748/16)
      - Damone, Vic (Box-folder 748/17)
      - Gorshin, Frank (Box-folder 748/18)
      - Kaye, Danny (Box-folder 748/19)
      - The King Daughters (Box-folder 748/20)
      - The King Sisters (Box-folder 748/21)
      - Lawrence, Carol (Box-folder 748/22)
      - Liberace (Box-folder 748/23)
      - Munshin, Jules (Box-folder 748/24)
      - The Pair Extraordinaire (Box-folder 748/25)
      - Rawls, Lou (Box-folder 748/26)
      - The Righteous Brothers (Box-folder 748/27)
      - Rodgers, Jimmy (Box-folder 748/28)
      - Schreiber & Burns (Box-folder 748/29)
      - The Smothers Brothers (Box-folder 748/30)
      - Sommers, Joanie (Box-folder 748/31)
      - Stevens, Connie (Box-folder 748/32)
      - Stevens, Inger (Box-folder 748/33)
      - Taylor, Faron (Box-folder 749/1)
      - Tillstrom, Burr (Box-folder 749/2)
      - Uggams, Leslie (Box-folder 749/3)
      - Williams, Roger (Box-folder 749/4)
    - Correspondence
      - A - Z (Box-folder 749/5)
    - Financial Reports: Shows
      - #1 - #6 (Box-folder 749/6)
      - #7 - #12 (Box-folder 749/7)
    - Invoices
      - American Federation of Musicians & Employees' Pension Welfare Fund (Box-folder 749/8)
      - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists & Welfare Funds (Box-folder 749/9)
      - "A" miscellaneous (Box-folder 749/10)
      - "B" miscellaneous (Box-folder 749/11)
      - CBS, 1966 (Box-folder 749/12, 750/1-2)
      - Corb, Morty (Box-folder 750/3)
      - "C" miscellaneous (Box-folder 750/4)
      - "D" miscellaneous (Box-folder 750/5)
      - "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 750/6)
      - John Gary Show (Box-folder 750/7)
      - Guy, Mr. (Box-folder 750/8)
      - "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 750/9)
      - Home Silk Stockings (Box-folder 750/10)
      - "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 750/11)
      - Kuehn, V.W. (Box-folder 750/12)
      - "I" "J" "K " miscellaneous (Box-folder 750/13)
      - "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 751/1)
      - "M" miscellaneous (Box-folder 751/2)
      - "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 751/3)
      - "O" "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 751/4)
      - "Q" "R" "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 751/5)
      - "T" "U" "V" miscellaneous (Box-folder 751/6)
      - "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 751/7)
      - Records, 1966 (Box-folder 751/8)
      - Reviews (Box-folder 729/5)
- Musical Comedy Library (Box 752-864, OV 865, OV 867, OV 869, 870-893)
  - Music
    - Musical Comedy Tonight
      Sheet music arranged alphabetically by song title.
      - Another hundred people (Box 752)
      - Anything goes (Box 752, OV 867)
      - I can't say no (Box 752, OV 867)
      - I get a kick out of you (Box 752, OV 867)
      - Overture (Box 753, OV 867)
      - Side insert (Box 753, OV 867)
    - Musical Comedy Tonight II
      - Big spender (Box 753, OV 867)
      - Circus dream (Box 753, OV 867)
      - Circus dream (live) (Box 753)
      - If this isn't love (Box 753, OV 867)
      - If my friends (Box 753, OV 867)
      - Jenny (Box 754, OV 867)
      - Jenny (verse live) (Box 754, OV 867)
      - Nothin' like a dame (Box 754)
      - Old devil moon and tag (Box 754, OV 867)
      - Overture (Box 754, OV 867)
      - P.22 fix (Box 754, OV 867)
      - See me now boys (Box 754, OV 867)
      - Wonderful guy (Box 754)
    - Musical Comedy Tonight III
      - Bows '85 (Box 755, OV 867)
      - Cleo bows (Box 755, OV 867)
      - Cleopatterer (Box 755, OV 867)
      - Eclipse scene (Box 756, OV 867)
      - Fascinatin' rhythm (dance) (Box 756, OV 867)
      - Fascinatin' rhythm (vocal) (Box 756, OV 867)
      - Heat wave (Box 756, OV 867)
      - Heat wave dance (Box 756, OV 867)
      - Leave it to Jane (Box 757, OV 867)
      - Overture (Box 757, OV 867)
      - They didn't believe me (Box 757, OV 867)
      - This can't be love (Box 758, OV 867)
      - Thou swell (Box 758, OV 867)
      - To keep my love alive (Box 758, OV 867)
      - To keep my love alive (revised) (Box 758, OV 867)
    - The Danny Kaye Show
      Parts (759-775) and score arrangements (OV 865). If only parts are available or only full score arrangements are available, only the one respective box will be listed.
      Arranged chronologically by show number and alphabetically by title therein.
      - #1, LC Record #95-502768
        - The baseball man (Box 759, OV 865)
        - Bye bye blackbird (Box 759)
        - Cleopatra's procession (Box 759)
        - Elijah jump shout (Box 759)
        - Film closing (Box 759)
        - Film opening (Box 759)
        - Love me Lady Powell (Box 759)
        - May there always be sunshine (Box 759)
        - My fair umpire (Box 759)
        - Riverside (Box 759, 760)
        - Walk around (Box 760)
        - Walk right in (Box 760)
        - West side story ballgame (Box 760)
      - #2, LC Record #95-503396
        - Brotherhood of man (Box 760)
        - Celestial choir (Box 760)
        - Forward in space (Box 760)
        - Streets of Laredo (Box 760)
        - Swinging march dance (Box 760)
        - Telephone (Box 760)
        - Three blind mice (Box 760)
        - To be or not to be (Box 760)
      - #3, LC Record #95-503412
        - La belle France (Box 760)
        - Biltmore clock (Box 760)
        - Clock song (I'm late) (Box 760)
        - Fools rush in (Box 760)
        - My grandfather's clock (Box 760)
        - Old MacDonald (Box 760)
        - Presentation time (Box 760)
        - Rock around the clock (Box 760)
        - Sonny's curls (Box 760)
        - Wake up George (Box 760)
      - #4, LC Record #95-503449
        - Dancing pagodas (Box 760)
        - Diner food (Box 760)
        - Lawrence ballet (Box 760)
        - Talent playhouse (Box 760)
        - Talent playoff (Box 760)
        - They call the wind Maria (Box 760)
        - This town tag (Box 760)
        - Together wherever we go (Box 760)
        - The victim (Box 760)
      - #5, LC Record #95-503551
        - Ballin' the jack (Box 760)
        - By myself (Box 760)
        - Danny - Love Lady duet (Box 760)
        - Days of wine and roses (Box 760)
        - Friend of the family (Box 760)
        - It's so nice to have a man around the house (Box 760)
        - Kaye-Kelly medley (Box 760)
        - Madame's waltz (Box 760)
        - Medley (Box 760)
        - New York, New York (Box 760)
        - Nola (Box 760)
        - Side by side (Box 760)
        - You make me feel so young (Box 760)
        - You'll never get away (Box 760)
        - You're the cream in my coffee (Box 760)
      - #6, LC Record #95-503706, #95-503715
        - Dee-lightful is the word (Box 761)
        - Father knows nothing (Box 761)
        - Father knows nothing (Box 761)
        - Father knows plenty (Box 761)
        - Hard hearted Hannah (Box 761)
        - I could write a book (Box 761)
        - Jungle drums (Box 761)
        - Mary Tyler Moore (Box 761)
        - Osaka hillbillies (Box 761)
        - Song and dance Man (Box 761)
        - Sposin' (Box 761)
        - Vaude playoff (Box 761)
      - #7, LC Record #95-503717
        - Alouette (Box 761)
        - Ashmolean (Box 761)
        - Children's suite (Box 761)
        - Drive in food (Box 761)
        - I get so lonely (Box 761)
        - Regal fanfare (Box 761)
        - Song and dance playoff (Box 761)
        - Two of a kind (Box 761)
        - What is a woman (Box 761)
      - #8, LC Record #95-503906
        - Arabian evenings (Box 761)
        - Gonna build a mountain (Box 761)
        - Get happy (Box 761)
        - Hospital bed (Box 761)
        - It's de-lovely (Box 761)
        - Michele (Box 761)
        - Once upon a lifetime (Box 761)
        - Tea for two (Box 761)
      - #9, LC Record #95-503909
        - Ach du lieber (Box 761)
        - Dingle dangle school (Box 761)
        - Everybody out of the pool (Box 761)
        - Fast drawers (Box 761)
        - Hungarian rhapsody (Box 761)
        - Kid's performance (Box 761)
        - Inter-office exercise (Box 761)
        - Lawrence of Arabia (Box 761)
        - My father (Box 761)
        - No manicure (Box 761)
        - Record shore (Box 761)
        - Stereo dance (Box 761)
        - Sugar in the morning (Box 761)
        - Top hat (Box 761)
      - #10, LC Record #95-503930
        - Angus McFangus (Box 761)
        - Breezin' along with the breeze (Box 761)
        - Come back again (Box 761)
        - Igor Dingiling (Box 761)
        - Johnny Ding-a-lingo (Box 761)
      - #11, LC Record #95-504257
        - Colonel Bogie (Box 762)
        - Coronation march (Box 762)
        - Fight (Box 762)
        - Fight fight fight (Box 762)
        - Happy hotel (Box 762)
        - Indian sign (Box 762)
        - Joannie Sommers (Box 762)
        - King Louie's song (Box 762)
        - Mozart musing (Box 762)
        - Romeo and Juliet (Box 762)
        - The story of Alice (Box 762)
      - #12, LC Record #95-504260
        - The Barber of Seville (Box 762)
        - Birth of the blues (Box 762)
        - Dance of the hours (1 & 2) (Box 762)
        - Danny Boy (Box 762)
        - Figaro (Box 762)
        - Good morning (Box 762)
        - Gypsy in my soul (Box 762)
        - Rigoletto (Box 762)
        - Surgery tonight (Box 762)
        - Tarantella (Box 762)
        - Toreador song (Box 762)
        - Turkish harem (Box 762)
        - Valkyries (Box 762)
        - Walk right in (Box 762)
      - #13, LC Record #95-504292
        - At last together (Box 762)
        - Blossoms tag (Box 762)
        - Closer walk (Box 762)
        - Fair maiden I have traveled long (Box 762)
        - Flower garden of my heart (Box 762)
        - Magnolia blossoms of 1932 (Box 762)
        - Make believe (Box 762)
        - Merrie England (Box 762)
        - Open up your heart (Box 762)
        - Professor Svengalsky (Box 762)
        - Transatlantic ride (Box 762)
        - When my sugar walks down the street (Box 762)
      - #14, LC Record #95-504305
        - British train (Box 762)
        - Bumble bee (Box 762)
        - Dancing mood (Box 762)
        - Hallelujah I love you (I love her so) (Box 762)
        - Jingle bells on and off (Box 762)
        - Timptation (Box 762)
      - #15, LC Record #95-504328
        - French medal (Box 762)
        - Simon says (Box 762)
        - Swingin' the news (Box 762)
        - Truly Julie Newmar (Box 762)
        - Wa wa (Box 762)
        - Yo ho (Box 762)
      - #16, LC Record #95-504337
        - Courtroom capers (Box 762)
        - Happy wedding (Box 762)
        - Hello ladies (Box 762)
        - Puttin' on the ritz (Box 762)
        - Santa's call (Box 762)
        - Spy dance (Box 762)
        - Verdict blues (Box 762)
        - Xmas season (Box 762)
        - You meet the nicest people (Box 762)
      - #17, LC Record #95-504339
        - Baby it's cold outside (Box 762)
        - Comes once in a lifetime (Box 762)
        - Dancing styles (Box 762)
        - In Vienna (Box 762)
        - Jingle journey (Box 762)
        - Old King Cole (Box 762)
        - That's how I feel (Box 762)
        - Vienna (reprise) (Box 762)
      - #18, LC Record #95-504343
        - Big Louie (Box 763)
        - Check for two (Box 763)
        - John Henry (Box 763)
        - Lazy river (Box 763)
        - Prison camp (Box 763)
        - Ship waiter (Box 763)
        - Tea (Box 763)
        - Tea is land (Box 763)
        - Tico tico (Box 763)
        - Vienna (Box 763)
        - We belong together (Box 763)
      - #19, LC Record #95-504361, #95-504365
        - Ain't it great to be crazy (Box 763)
        - Duck blind (Box 763)
        - Hit parade medley
          - 1. Close as pages in a book (Box 763)
          - 2. High on a windy hill (Box 763)
          - 3. Hold me (Box 763)
          - 4. It only happens when I dance with you (Box 763)
          - 5. Three little words (Box 763)
          - 6. The boy next door (Box 763)
          - 7. Something's coming (Box 763)
          - 8. When a gypsy makes his violin cry (Box 763)
          - 9. Hands across the table (Box 763)
        - I wish you love (Box 763)
        - I won't dance (Box 763)
        - Magnum studios (Box 763)
        - Marriage counselor (Box 763)
        - My walking cane (Box 763)
      - #20, LC Record #95-504373
        - Birthday surprise (Box 763)
        - Blues dance (1 & 2) (Box 763)
        - Grand lummox march (Box 763)
        - I like the likes of you (Box 763)
        - Ox drivers song (Box 763)
        - Pine concerto (Box 763)
        - Safety zone (Box 763)
      - #21, LC Record #95-504377
        - Chapanecas (Box 763)
        - Diahann Carroll (Box 763)
        - Father and the nurse (Box 763)
        - Fight game (Box 763)
        - Here comes the bride (Box 763)
        - Jazz dance closing (Box 763)
        - Put on a happy face (Box 763)
        - Spanish hat theme (Box 763)
        - Table dance (Box 763)
        - Three o'clock (Box 763)
        - Viva papata (Box 763)
        - Wedding march (Box 763)
      - #22, LC Record #95-504540
        - Action station (Box 763)
        - Can can impressions (Box 763)
        - Competition time (Box 763)
        - Crazy Barbara (Box 763)
        - He's a mountie (Box 763)
        - He's a mountie (closing) (Box 763)
        - Marching along together (Box 763)
        - Mountie B.G. (Box 763)
        - Mr. Hummingbird (Box 763)
        - San Francisco Bay blues (Box 763)
        - Saskatchewan (Box 763)
        - Shall we dance (Box 763)
        - Swiss ambassador (1-3) (Box 763)
      - #23, LC Record #95-504782
        - Beethoven minuet (Box 763)
        - English judge (Box 763)
        - H.M.S. Cruelty (Box 763)
        - Just in time (Box 763)
        - Minuet in "G" (Box 763)
        - Teen-ager (Box 763)
        - Thru the customs (Box 763)
        - When I take my sugar to tea (Box 763)
        - With a shine on your shoes (Box 763)
      - #24, LC Record #95-504862
        - Finale - hillbilly sketch (Box 763)
        - Hey look me over (Box 763)
        - I caught a bear (Box 763)
        - I didn't catch an owl (Box 763)
        - Let's take a walk (Box 763)
        - Marching along (Box 763)
        - Pappy Clunk (Box 763)
        - Secret service (Box 763)
        - Soon it's gonna rain (Box 763)
        - Uninvited guest (Box 763)
        - Wonderful guy (Box 763)
      - #25, LC Record #95-505229
        - Down by the Winegar Wolks (Box 763)
        - Flamenco capers (Box 763)
        - Now is the hour (Box 763)
        - Proposal time (Box 763)
        - Sevilla (Box 763)
        - They all laughed (Box 763)
      - #26, LC Record #95-505041
        - Dr. Yes (Box 764)
        - King Tut (Box 764)
        - I Love a piano (Box 764)
        - Mama Luigi's (Box 764)
        - The music stopped (Box 764)
        - Yankee Doodle (Box 764)
      - #27, LC Record #95-505143
        - Desert camel blues (Box 764)
        - Desert closing (Box 764)
        - Desert men (Box 764)
        - Heart of my heart (Box 764)
        - Old fashioned (Box 764)
        - Surfside baby (Box 764)
        - Time to hit (Box 764)
        - You're under arrest (Box 764)
      - #28, LC Record #95-505230
        - Alone together (Box 764)
        - Blast off (Box 764)
        - Change partners (Box 764)
        - Consider yourself (Box 764)
        - Cup of coffee (Box 764)
        - Friendship club (Box 764)
        - Hit parade medley #1-#9,#11-#14 (Box 764)
        - It's that time of the year (Box 764)
        - Manhattan (Box 764)
        - Tequila mockingbird (Box 764)
        - Vienna woods (Box 764)
        - Where or when (Box 764)
      - #29, LC Record #95-505406, #95-505454
        - Gigi (Box 764)
        - I ain't down yet (Box 764)
        - Long hot supper (Box 764)
        - Look out for mama (Box 764)
        - Western impressions (Box 764)
        - Whistle while you work (Box 764)
      - #30, LC Record #95-505559
        - Marriage pronounciation (Box 764)
        - Roberta and the maid (Box 764)
        - Steppin' with my baby (Box 764)
        - 30's production (1-4) (Box 764)
      - #31, LC Record #95-505681
        - Around the world (Box 764)
        - Art gallery (Box 764)
        - Ballin' the jack (Box 764)
        - Irish mother (Box 764)
        - My lady loves to dance (Box 764)
        - Suite for odd -ball instruments (Box 764)
        - This way please (Box 764)
      - #32, LC Record #95-505758, #95-506185
        - Barber chair switch (Box 764)
        - Danny Boy Italian (Box 764)
        - Donna Reed theme (Box 764)
        - Farewell Cindy Jane (Box 764)
        - I'll remember April (Box 764)
        - Late spot (Box 764)
        - Mention my name in Sheboygan (Box 764)
        - Mountain greenery (Box 764)
        - Nursies (Box 764)
        - Petticoat junction (Box 764)
      - #33, LC Record #95-506002
        - Argument anatomy (Box 764)
        - Big elopement (Box 764)
        - Cope with the pony (1-3) (Box 764)
        - The fair in a day (Box 764)
        - Here's Danny (Box 764)
        - I've got your number (Box 764)
        - Just in time (Box 764)
        - On stage (Box 764)
        - Water boy (Box 764)
      - #34, LC Record #95-506008
        - A buddy by the name of "You" (Box 765)
        - Lulu's back in town (Box 765)
        - Night with the pirahnas (Box 765)
        - On the street (Box 765)
      - #35, LC Record #95-506488
        - Blind date (Box 765)
        - Foggy day (Box 765)
        - Huckleberry duck (Box 765)
        - What is love (Box 765)
      - #36, LC Record #95-506557
        - Broadway wedding (Box 765)
        - Deadwood stage (Box 765)
        - Green socks (Box 765)
        - Little Dutch treat (Box 765)
        - On to New Haven (Box 765)
        - Runnin' wild (Box 765)
        - Sad Bernie (Box 765)
        - The show's a hit (Box 765)
        - The tapioca (Box 765)
        - They call the wind Maria (Box 765)
      - #37, LC Record #95-506611, #95-507058, #95-507063
        - Ain't she sweet (Box 765)
        - Bidin' my time (Box 765)
        - Checkstand four (Box 765)
        - Cindy Sue (Box 765)
        - Mountain feud (Box 765)
        - Sentimental journey (Box 765)
        - T.V. waltz revels (Box 765)
      - #38, LC Record #95-507692
        - The ballad of Red Ridin' Hood (Box 765)
        - Control yourself (Box 765)
        - English courtroom (Box 765)
        - I get along without you (Box 765)
        - Look who's dancing (Box 765)
        - Paper clip job (Box 765)
      - #39, LC Record #95-507895
        - Ain't nobody here but us chickens (Box 765)
        - Arabian music (Box 765)
        - Candy butcher playoff (Box 765)
        - Don't put a tax (Box 765)
        - Jamboree Jones (Box 765)
        - Japanese sunset (Box OV 865)
        - Lady of Spain (Box 765)
        - Late night party (Box 765)
        - You make me feel so young (Box 765)
        - You're my everything (Box 765)
      - #40, LC Record #95-508025
        - The first day (Box 765)
        - The gift (Box 765)
        - Gypsy camp (Box 765)
        - A gypsy cries (Box 765)
        - Gypsy life (Box 765)
        - Gypsy wedding (Box 765)
        - Hey gypsy (Box 765)
        - Marching adorables (Box 765)
        - No strings (Box 765)
        - They'll never break us (Box 765)
        - Where is the man (Box 765)
      - #41, LC Record #95-508243
        - British murder (Box 765)
        - Fat on a hot tin roof (Box 765)
        - I've got a loverly bunch (Box 765)
        - Jonathon Edwards playoff (Box 765)
        - Let's watch television (Box 765)
        - Piano roll blues (Box 765)
        - Spelling song (Box 765)
        - Ten cents a dance (Box 765)
      - #42, LC Record #95-508332, #95-508359
        - Balloon dance (Box 765)
        - Fire the maid (Box 765)
        - Here I'll stay (Box 765, OV 865)
        - Medley (pennies-nevertheless) (Box 765)
        - Slap that bass (Box 765)
        - Way back home (Box 765)
      - #43, LC Record #95-508405
        - The amateur doctor (Box 766)
        - Anvil playoff (Box 766)
        - Do're'mi' (Box 766)
        - Heart alone (Box 766)
        - The Irish traveller (Box 766)
        - Laura (Box 766)
        - Stairway to heaven (Box 766)
      - #44, LC Record #95-508565
        - Cherry pie (Box 766)
        - Italian group singer (Box 766)
        - Rehearsal hall revue (Box 766)
        - Turkey with stuffing (Box 766)
        - You are my sunshine (Box 766)
      - #45, LC Record #95-508803
        - Circus impressions (Box 766)
        - Flight (Box 766)
        - Personality (Box 766)
        - Pick yourself up (Box 766)
        - The questions children ask (Box 766)
        - This is the army (Box 766)
        - Up above my head (Box 766)
      - #46, LC Record #95-508805
        - Act I & act II (Box 766)
        - Act II & act III (Box 766)
        - The best things (Box 766)
        - Broadway (Box 766)
        - Don Chernandos song (Box 766)
        - Drive to work (Box 766)
        - Japanese teenager (Box 766)
        - If this isn't love (Box 766)
        - Mother goose on the loose (Box 766)
        - Murder maestro please (Box 766)
        - Our two hearts (Box 766)
        - Public lover #1 (Box 766)
        - The trouble song (Box 766)
        - The trouble song (finale) (Box 766)
        - We're the sailor boys (Box 766)
        - Who wants to be a millionaire (Box 766)
      - #47, LC Record #95-508806
        - Cute dance (Box 766)
        - Old MacDonald (Box 766)
        - Santa Claus Rudy (Box 766)
        - Space capsule (Box 766)
        - Swan Lake (Box 766)
      - #48, LC Record #95-508981
        - Changing of the guard (Box 766)
        - Didn't it rain (Box 766)
        - Frere Jacques (Box 766)
        - Heavenly music (Box 766)
        - Luncheon with history (Box 766)
        - Oh promise me (Box 766, OV 865)
      - #49, LC Record #95-508998
        - Christmas fantasy (Box 766)
        - Fanfares (Box 766)
        - He's gone away (Box 766)
        - The spy (Box 766)
        - Villie villie (Box 766)
        - Waltz around the Christmas tree (Box 766)
        - Xmas waltz (intro) (Box 766)
      - #50, LC Record #95-509142
        - Hit parade #1-#14 (Box 766)
        - I'm beginning to see the light (Box 766)
        - Pretty baby (Box 766)
        - El ringo (Box 766)
        - Tacos please (Box 766)
        - What is this thing (Box 766)
      - #51, LC Record #95-509142
        - Big time scientist (Box 766)
        - Come rain or come shine (Box 766)
        - I like flying (Box 766)
        - Jerome at the dentist (Box 766)
        - Too long at the fair (Box 766)
        - Triplets (Box 766)
        - Variations in rhythm (Box 766)
      - #52, LC Record #95-509303
        - Acrobat opening (Box 766)
        - Circus II (Box 766)
        - Hitchcock movie (Box 766)
        - How to laugh (Box 766)
        - Italian movie (Box 766)
        - Life is just a bunch of cherries (Box 766)
        - Play a simple melody (Box 766)
        - Russian Cinderella (Box 766)
        - Seymour and the gladiators (Box 766)
        - Walt Disney movie (Box 766)
      - #53, LC Record #95-509315
        - Big bad wolf (Box 767)